It's supposed to be a doozy.
How are you doing? How are you?
How are you?
I'm very well.
You know why I called you here today?
Did I do something wrong?
Well, that might be the short answer.
Yeah, I'll take it off.
You're facing multiple charges.
Multiple?
Multiple charges.
You aware of that?
I don't know. I don't know...
I don't...
Well, I'll tell you one at a time, then, for you.
Yes, please.
On-site catering request.
I've got a lot of snacks!
Oh, my God...
Are you aware of this?
Yes, I am.
You're scaring me!
How is this a bad thing?
What's wrong?
You know what?
I don't know.
It's a piggyback!
What's a scoff?
Shame harassment.
What's that?
I'm saying it's when the whole room smells like a snack.
I'm really sorry, it's just...
There's been a lot of evidence about it.
Evidence?
Squid, beef jerky, cucumbers.
Basically, you only request things with a strong smell.Basically, you only request things with a strong smell.
I'm sorry, sir.
What do you think about that?
I wasn't thinking about it.
I was only thinking about myself.
I was only thinking about my own stomach.
That's very important...
Eat up, eat up.
I just got a cold one.
Oh, well...
But these charges...
It's a very serious charge.
I see.
Can I eat it?
I didn't say no.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm just asking for a percentage.
I'm trying to reduce it.
I'm just saying we should think about it.
Oh, well...
This is a lesser charge.
It's the lesser of two evils.
It's a crime.
I called you here for a different reason.
The next one.
Taking a picture of yourself with someone's phone.
Did you take a picture? Selfie!
No, I didn't.
Next thing you know, you've got an extra set of false teeth on your holder.
I didn't take it.
Yes, you did.
Is it unconscious?
Well, maybe it's an unconscious phase.
I don't know.
You deny it? We've got a lot of evidence.Deny it? Numerous pieces of evidence have come to light.
Evidence?
We've got evidence. We've got witnesses.
I didn't take any pictures.
Do you deny it?
Yes, sir.
I didn't film it.
You don't remember taking it?
I don't remember. I didn't do it.
You're lying!
I don't admit it.
You're being falsely accused.
Me?
I'm the one.
It's me.
It's good that you're aware of what you're doing.
In this case...
I'm told there's been some damage.
You're free!
Yeah! You're free!
Well, it's a little bit...
This is a tough one.
It's gonna be hard.
You're really getting into it. It's interesting.
Oh, no, it's difficult.
Well, I guess I'll just say you're free.
Can I come around this side?
Sure.
Let's just keep adding to it.
Yuji Oda Bridge
Released.
Sit down!
Excuse me, excuse me.
Yamaguchi KirashiYamaguchi Kirashi
KIRASHI YAMAGUCHI
Are you okay?
How are you?
Yes, I'm very well.
Is it possible that you're smiling so broadly?
No, it's just... this kind of atmosphere.
It's too funny.
You know, you're facing a number of charges.
Yes, sir.
Seriously.
Let's start with what you did.
First of all, what did I do?
Remember what you did to the others.
Remember what you've done to others.
Recently.
A few years ago.
No, nothing like that.
It's not like that.
You are.
Yes, I am.
It was a staple of the show when it was called "Ohasuta".
Kiran
Dazzling.
I had the other site staff do it too.
What the hell!
By the way, that's very recent.
Recently?
I'm a little disappointed that I missed it until now.
I'm a little disappointed that I missed it.
Are you aware of this?
I don't feel bad about it.
And the staff...And the staff.
They were very happy to see me.
as a mystery case.
I see.
Let's give it a try.
Are you sure?
I'm in.
What's your name?
Misaki Tsurutani.
Why are you crying?
Obakutan.
It's difficult.
I'm Oda! Oda! Get it right!
Yes, laser.
May I?
Misaki, Yuzawa!
Blink!
It's so bright!
No, this one,
It's heavy.
You're making me think I'm gonna like you.
I'm falling for it.
You're good.
You're taking the stuff from your fasta days
He's taking it to other places.
That's a very serious crime.
I should be aware of that.
I wasn't aware of it, and now I'm aware of it again.
I'm sorry.
What are your plans for the future?
I'm going to keep doing what I'm doing.
I'll keep playing the killer.
I'll get us all involved again.
No, sir. I won't be doing that anymore.It's a lie. I won't do it again in the future.
Yes, you are.
A little bit of this manager, too.
Maybe it was awkward at this point.
Coming in here as a habituation...
Excuse me.
Can I ask you something?
I'll, uh...
Good night.
I think the manager is guilty of this.
Kira Yamaguchi, you're free to go.
Thank you.
But...
Ogawa Youka, huh?
Sit down.
please.
You know what this place is?
What do you think this place is?
Study group.
Don't be coy.
Well, there's more than one suspect.
I have multiple charges against you.
Let's take them one at a time.
There was that music video shoot.
The Jagga Jagga Jungle.
It was a long shoot.
You know...
It was a very tense shoot downstairs.
We had a dressing room upstairs.
Do you remember what you were doing up there?
I was dancing to my senior's music.
That's not what you were doing.
I remember.
Sweet potatoes?
You were performing with a sweet potato as a mikrol.
Remember that?Remember me?
You remember me.
I remember.
What was your performance?
What song were you playing?
We were performing Strawberry Sadistic in front of everybody.
Why sweet potatoes?
I just happened to have a sweet potato with me.
But I love sweet potatoes.
Sweet potatoes are heavy.
It's food!
Mike!
Food!
I have to apologize.
I should apologize to the sweet potatoes, too.
It'll be a relief.
What is this?
What's this?
It's a chicken and egg bowl because it wasn't triggered.
Well, that was fun.
It was fun.
Everyone laughed.
That's right.
But they did warn you that it was a little loud.
You don't know what you're doing.
This is heavy.
It's heavy.
And you know it.
You're talking while you're putting it in your mouth.
Well, I'll give you one more thing to finish it off.
One more thing to top it off.
And you.
There's a short and late charge...
That's right, isn't it?
A short and slow one.Short and slow sins.
Indeed.
What do you think about this?
No, but...
I admit that I'm slow.
I admit to being slow.
I admit it's slow.
I understand that you're not trying to slow me down.
I understand.
No one thinks that.
I'm trying to slow you down.
I was already last yesterday.
Last minute plus.
I had to leave in a hurry with all my stuff spread out on my desk.
So let Minami and I carry it.
In my backpack.
Last thing.
And that one.
Is that okay?
Can you explain yourself?
We're often the last to leave, aren't we?
That's a lot.
I'm cleaning up after everyone else.
This way.
This is for everyone.
I'm putting all the chairs and stuff back.
We're putting them back.
What do you think?
I'll have to gather evidence on that.
Actually...
Have you ever actually seen him do that?
Oh.
He's proud of his victory.
Damn.
What about me?how about you, ogawashi?
Hmmm, well, it's a service spirit. All of it.
Kitsuho!
Um, I, um, Tsuruya City is also getting the hang of it!
That's right!
Please, this way...
Tsuruya City?
Wait a minute!
Tsuruya City has a letter of invitation too, and you've been doing it all day like such a big shot.
Please sit down.
Sit down!
What's wrong with my back?
Do you have any idea?
No. I swear I don't.
You sure?
I'm proud of what I do.
Pride isn't enough?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Mm-hmm.
A thousand percent!
Really?
I don't swear to God.
There's food in front of you.
Are you sure?
I didn't swear on a bird.
When we were filming for the Galgal Channel.
I spilled some food on it and it stained my costume.
I've been skipping the white costume ever since.
Today I had an accident.
I'm happy to announce that the ban on white costumes has been lifted today.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
But...
Finally, we've had an accident
I know how much you usually spill, dear.I know how much you usually spill, dear.
What do you think of each one?
I've certainly spilled.
And...
I've spilled it and I've been so impatient.
I've gone to the makeup artist to clean it up.
I've used makeup remover to clean it off with.
I've wondered if they'd notice.
You've been exposed. All of it.
But isn't it good to talk about having an accident?
You're wearing white today.
I'm feeling sorry for myself.
I can see you're sorry.
I'd like to change my clothes, put on a convenience store bag or something.
Yes, that's right.
My foundation made it.
I've seen her change her clothes with an empty convenience store bag.
I'm sorry about that.
Maybe there's something you'd like to say to me so I don't mess up my costume again.
Face covers, plastic bags...
I'm trying not to get my costume dirty.
I'm trying not to get it dirty.
Okay.
We're good to go.
You're free to go.
Thank you very much.
I'm wearing T Hollick's costume this time.